<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://design-o.github.io/orss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-07-04T12:13:06.519Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://design-o.github.io/orss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://design-o.github.io/orss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vale – Bob Mouatt (OAM)]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11480</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/vale-bob-mouatt-oam/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T20:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Australia is saddened to learn of the passing of one of our former Presidents in Bob. Bob was a true icon of our sport. He was a leader, promoter, communicator, manager, organiser, planner, controller, competitor, and mentor. Bob gave so much to our sport as a passionate member of Orienteering ACT and with Orienteering Australia.
Vale – Bob Mouatt (OAM) first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaeldowling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWOC Long distance: Bührer wins second gold, Czech reign in W20]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72457</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/jwoc-buhrer-wins-second-gold-on-long-czech-reign-in-w20/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was total Czech dominance in the women’s class as the Junior World Orienteering Championships field went into the forest today for the long distance, where Switzerland’s Matthieu Bührer took the title for the second consecutive day in the men’s class. After two days of sprint races, Wednesday offered a completely different challenge for the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oceania NZ 2025 Embargoes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59927</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/oceania-nz-embargoes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T11:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone intending to enter the Oceania Orienteering Championships 24-27 January 2025 needs to be aware of the embargoes in place for the event. Embargoes are areas that are out of bounds to competitors prior to the events, and cover the areas being used in the competition. This prevents unfair prior knowledge being gained about the […]
Oceania NZ 2025 Embargoes first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joolz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walpole and Lammas Parks Results]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22174</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/racereports/walpole-lammas-results-jul24/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T07:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many thanks to Don for mapping and planning some intricate London parks, brand new to orienteering. Results – pdf Results – SPORTident WinSplits (split times [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Clelland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOC 2024 Test Races]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11462</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/woc-2024-test-races/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T07:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six Australian athletes raced in the WOC 2024 Test Races in Edinburgh in preparation for WOC next week.
WOC 2024 Test Races first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Orienteering Championships 2024 – team announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.ie/?p=18412</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.ie/world-orienteering-championships-2024-team-announcement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=world-orienteering-championships-2024-team-announcement"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T13:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jens Waechter, Orienteering Ireland’s High Performance Manager, today announced the team for the World Orienteering Sprint Championships 2024 taking place in Edinburgh 11-16 July. Congratulations to all on your selection. Sprint Male Sprint Female Knock-Out Sprint Male  Knock-Out Sprint Female Relay Team 1
The post World Orienteering Championships 2024 – team announcement first appeared on Orienteering in Ireland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deirdre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWOC: Shared sprint gold in W20, narrow Swiss win in M20]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72444</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/jwoc-shared-sprint-gold-in-w20-narrow-swiss-win-in-m20/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The teams and spectators at the Junior World Orienteering Championship in Czechia saw a thrilling sprint race on Tuesday, where Elli Punto (FIN) and Michaela Novotna (CZE) tied for the gold in the women’s class, and Switzerland’s Matthieu Bührer won by two seconds in the men’s. Today’s sprint took place in the historic city centre […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Eef van Dongen on WOC in Scotland and her Knock-Out Sprint bronze from Denmark in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72439</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/podcast-eef-van-dongen-on-woc-in-scotland-and-her-knock-out-sprint-bronze-from-denmark-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T09:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With only four years of orienteering experience, Eef van Dongen (NED) took the orienteering world by surprise, when she won the bronze medal as Knock-Out Sprint made its debut on the WOC-program in Denmark in 2022. In this podcast episode, she shares her memories from the day and look ahead to the upcoming World Orienteering […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWOC: Norway took clear Sprint Relay win]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72428</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/jwoc-norway-took-clear-sprint-relay-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T21:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norway took the first gold medal at the Junior World Orienteering Championships, which began on Monday afternoon with a sprint relay in the western part of Pilsen city, Czechia. An impressive 77 teams were ready at the starting line at 16.15, when the championships were kicked off in front of an enthusiastic audience. Today’s arena […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southern Cross Teams are now official]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59909</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/southern-cross-teams-are-now-official/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T19:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the deadline passing for appeals for this year’s Southern Cross Teams, ONZ is happy to officially confirm teams and management below. Participants will each be invoiced the first of three involves for the trip this week. A second invoice will be sent closer to departure, with a final invoice after the trip’s return to […]
Southern Cross Teams are now official first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EYOC 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.ie/?p=18390</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.ie/eyoc-2024/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=eyoc-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T10:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Irish Junior Team recently took part in the 2024 European Youth Orienteering Championships, held in Szczecin, Poland from June 21st – June 24th. The team this year was the largest ever sent to EYOC, with 13 athletes selected to represent Ireland. This was the best team result for Ireland at EYOC so far (22nd […]
The post EYOC 2024 first appeared on Orienteering in Ireland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deirdre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compass Point – June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59924</id>
        <link href="https://mailchi.mp/orienteering.org.nz/compass-point-june-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T10:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View this content here: https://mailchi.mp/orienteering.org.nz/compass-point-june-2024 M e m b e r n e w s & v i e w s | J U N E 2 0 2 4Submissions welcome by the 20th of each month Jan - Nov. Email here (mailto:editor@orienteering.org.nz?subject=Compass%20Point%20submission)U p d a t e* Notes from the GM* View from the […]
Compass Point – June 2024 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View from the Chair | June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59893</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/orienteering-nz/view-from-the-chair-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Board met last week and health and safety has been a focus, especially with a couple of recent serious incidents at events we will be sharing the learnings from reviewing these. Spoiler alert…the clubs on the ground had excellent responses and are great examples of good practice to share. At the Board level we’ve had […]
View from the Chair | June 2024 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup |Round Two, Genoa Italy | 1-2 June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59889</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/world-cup-round-two-genoa-italy-1-2-june/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sprint – 1 JuneTim tackled a challenging map in the individual sprint race with composure, pushing hard to secure 7th place. The race began with a highly technical garden section and a steep hill, descending into the older town buildings. Amber noted similarities to the Wellington Botanic Gardens map at the start, while Laura appreciated […]
World Cup |Round Two, Genoa Italy | 1-2 June  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EYOC  |Szcezecin, Poland | 22-24 June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59883</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/junior-2/eyoc-szcezecin-poland-22-24-june/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From June 22nd to 24th, fourteen young New Zealand athletes travelled to Poland to participate in the European Youth Orienteering Championships. On Saturday, June 22nd, the competition kicked off with the long-distance event. Rachel Baker and Tide Fa’avae both achieved commendable results, placing 18th and 20th respectively in the W18 category. Eddie Swain led the […]
EYOC  |Szcezecin, Poland | 22-24 June  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[King’s Birthday Weekend| Nelson Orienteering Club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59874</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/blog/kings-birthday-weekend-nelson-orienteering-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[King’s Birthday Weekend saw over 450 participants tackle the ‘Middle’ event at Canaan Downs, in tricky, highly technical terrain. Planner Amelia Horne and controller Calum Coombs had made most of the rolling farmland and moderate to fast open beech forest with intricate karst topography, numerous tomos and marble rock outcrops, resulting in a lot of […]
King’s Birthday Weekend| Nelson Orienteering Club first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinestars v’s Bushrangers  | King’s Birthday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59871</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/blog/pinestars-vs-bushrangers-kings-birthday/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bushrangers
Pinestars v’s Bushrangers  | King’s Birthday  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oceania Orienteering Championships 2025 |  24-27 January]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59868</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/oceania-orienteering-championships-2025-24-27-january/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us in the summer of 2025 for an unforgettable orienteering adventure through the stunning sand dunes and pines of the Manawatū. Our races will challenge your navigation skills and decision-making across a variety of fast and intricate forest maps. Oceania 2025 events are designed to provide elite orienteers with ideal training and competition grounds […]
Oceania Orienteering Championships 2025 |  24-27 January  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great Forest Rogaine | Rotorua – 27 July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59865</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/rogaining/great-forest-rogaine-rotorua-27-july/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get together a team for a great adventure in Whakarewarewa forest, Rotorua. Orienteering BOP is delighted to invite all previous competitors, and those newcomers wanting to enjoy a great adventure with their team mates, to the 2024 Great Forest Rogaine (GFR). GFR is a 3 or 6 hour, foot or mountain bike team rogaine open […]
Great Forest Rogaine | Rotorua – 27 July first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Orienteering Championship Carnival 2024  |  AOC 24]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59862</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/schools/australian-orienteering-championship-carnival-2024-aoc-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Armidale/Uralla region is the location for this years AOC. It is a section of the Granite Belt which runs along the Great Dividing Range. The Granite Belt has played host to many State and National competitions. Championship events.:The Australian Middle, Relay and Long Championships will all be held on a new map. The same […]
Australian Orienteering Championship Carnival 2024  |  AOC 24  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NZ Secondary Schools Orienteering Champs | 19 -21 July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59859</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/nz-secondary-schools-orienteering-champs-19-21-july/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Wellington is looking forward to welcoming all year 7-13 orienteers from across New Zealand to the Wellington region for three days of high-quality orienteering from the 19th-21st July 2024. Join us and showcase your navigational skills, support your friends and create lasting memories in unique terrain. The events are located north of Wellington, towards the Kapiti Coast.All […]
NZ Secondary Schools Orienteering Champs | 19 -21 July first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manawatū Schools Relay | 2 August]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59856</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/manawatu-schools-relay-2-august/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Manawatū Schools Relay Champs will be August 2nd. Let your school know to plan the teams. Students run in teams of 3. Online entries close 24 July. The event fee is $5 each including ident hire. Categories: year 5/6,  7/8 boys/ girls and secondary girls / boys.  For more details email
Manawatū Schools Relay | 2 August first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short history of orienteering in New Zealand  |  50 years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59853</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/orienteering-nz/short-history-of-orienteering-in-new-zealand-50-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year marked our 50th anniversary, and Bryan Teehan compiled a special booklet for the occasion. Meanwhile, Stuart Payne wearing a moonboot, was easily persuaded to update our 40-year-old history and extend it by another decade. The resulting 52-page document commemorates the 50th Anniversary of ONZ (formerly NZOF). When asked about the task of adding […]
Short history of orienteering in New Zealand  |  50 years  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southern Cross Challenge Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59850</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/southern-cross-challenge-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team SelectionSelectors have published this year’s Southern Cross Team which will be officially approved shortly subject to ONZ’s appeal deadlines passing. This year’s team features athletes from Southland, PAPO, Nelson, Wellington, Red Kiwis, OBOP, Hawkes Bay, Waikato, Auckland and Counties Manukau – members from 2/3s of ONZ’s Clubs!  It is the first time in a number of years that […]
Southern Cross Challenge Update first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteers in GodZone documentary | NZ Mountain Film Festival]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59846</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/blog/orienteers-in-godzone-documentary-nz-mountain-film-festival/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteers in GodZone documentary |  NZ Mountain Film Festival  The Adventure of Racing follows is a documentary of a female-led adventure racing team. Film maker Ben Wallbank, follows the team competing in GodZone which was also the Adventure Racing World Championships in Fiordland, New Zealand. The documentary picked up a best documentary award for the work on exposing the challenges of […]
Orienteers in GodZone documentary | NZ Mountain Film Festival  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONZ’s Board approve new HP staffing structure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59843</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/onzs-board-approve-new-hp-staffing-structure/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the retirement of long-serving ONZ Performance Leader Malcolm Ingham earlier in the year, ONZ’s Board reached out to key stakeholders to review how High Performance (HP) should be staffed over the next five years. The group included current and form elite athletes, coaches, Board Members, current and former Club Presidents and a Regional Development […]
ONZ’s Board approve new HP staffing structure  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back stage business   |  The tech behind the Aus 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59839</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/back-stage-business-the-tech-behind-the-aus-3-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A re-printed article with permission from the Orienteering Australia e-news and the Orienteering South Australian magazine. This is a detailed log of all the tech activities tracked before, during and after the Aus 3 Days including the preparation, setup, running, adapting to changes and keeping track of entries and results. It is a dedicated description on the functions of tech as part of […]
Back stage business   |  The tech behind the Aus 3 Days first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bendigo Bush – Mosquito Creek – Saturday 6 July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13733</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/bendigo-bush-mosquito-creek-saturday-6-july/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T06:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Barr has recently completed a remap of Mosquito Creek and this event will be its first use. The contours are all new, based upon very recent lidar data, but expect the same challenges to test your orienteering skills.
Bendigo Bush – Mosquito Creek – Saturday 6 July first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margi Freemantle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWOC 2024: All You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://news.worldofo.com/?p=20110</id>
        <link href="https://news.worldofo.com/2024/07/01/jwoc-2024-all-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T03:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[LIVE from Monday July 1st 16:00 CET] The Junior World Orienteering Championships (JWOC) 2024 in Czech Republic starts with the Sprint Relay on Monday July 1st, continues with Sprint on Tuesday, Long on Wednesday, Middle on Friday and finishes off with Relay on Saturday.  The championship is organized around Pilsen, Czech Republic – and will offer a full webTV-broadcast at IOF TV (25 ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Kocbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victorians Sprint to Success at JWOC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13703</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/victorians-selected-to-australian-teams-who-where-and-when/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T05:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow JWOC in Czechia from Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72413</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/follow-jwoc-in-czechia-from-monday/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T10:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international highlight of the year for junior orienteers begins on Monday when the Junior World Orienteering Championships kick off in Pilsen, Czechia. More than 330 athletes from 38 nations have registered for the championships, which count five races during JWOC week. The youngest discipline on the programme, Sprint Relay gets the party started before […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British Sprint Orienteering Championships]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11440</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/british-sprint-orienteering-championships/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a strong team for the mixed sprint relay at the British Sprint Orienteering Championships, the team finished 4th overall.
British Sprint Orienteering Championships first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the SOA Board – June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54144</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/meet-the-soa-board-june-2024/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=meet-the-soa-board-june-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T19:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the June 2024 AGM, we thought now was a pertinent time to give you a bit of background about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Youth Orienteering Championships Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11409</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/european-youth-orienteering-championships-recap/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia had 5 athletes competing in Szczecin, Poland in the 2024 EYOC, the largest competition in the IOF calendar.
European Youth Orienteering Championships Recap first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia-NZ challenge 2024 MTBO selection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59831</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/australia-nz-challenge-2024-mtbo-selection/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T23:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the MTBO selected team for the Australia-NZ challenge at the AustralianMTBO Champs in October 2024 Selection into the MTBO squad is made according to the relevant Selection Policy and guidelines for MTBO selectors. 
Australia-NZ challenge 2024 MTBO selection first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joolz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British Sprint Weekend 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22147</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/clubnews/bsc2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T18:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several SLOW members enjoyed the British Sprint Relays and the British Sprint Championships in the Midlands on the weekend 22-23rd June. Everyone found a way [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vinh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Northern Ireland 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5802</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/the-northern-ireland-3-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T13:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 3 NI events in a week (and more club events and activities besides), it’s been a busy start to the summer. First off was the second event in the 2024 NI Urban League at South Craigavon on 16 June, with Graeme Francis’ extended map...
The post The Northern Ireland 3 Days appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silver medal at European Youth Orienteering Championships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54119</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/silver-medal-at-european-youth-orienteering-championships/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=silver-medal-at-european-youth-orienteering-championships"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T10:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish runners enjoyed some success in Poland at the weekend, with James Hammond (Forth Valley Orienteers) taking a silver medal in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vic MTBO Series, Sunday 7 July, Tallarook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13333</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/vic-mtbo-series-1-sunday-24-march-creswick/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T02:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Vic Series MTBO event is on 7 July, on a new map at Tallarook
Vic MTBO Series, Sunday 7 July, Tallarook first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Southern Cross Teams Named]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59817</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/2024-southern-cross-teams-named/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ONZ selection panel has named this year’s teams to contest the Southern Cross Team in Australia: Karahiwi Senior Boys: Oscar Burns, Cody Carter, Jake McLellan, Blake McKinnon, Solomon Randerson Senior Girls: Anna Babington, Phoebe Hunt, Alicia McGivern, Amy Nicoll, Nika Rayward Junior Boys: Harley Brennan (Subject to fitness), Arya Chebbi, Micah Dunn, Charlie Milne, […]
2024 Southern Cross Teams Named first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EYOC: Relay wins for Finland, Hungary, Czechia and Sweden]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72130</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/eyoc-relay-wins-for-finland-hungary-czechia-and-sweden/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monday’s relays were the last race at the 2024 European Youth Orienteering Championships in Szczechin, Poland. The more than 400 athletes were back in the forest after yesterday’s sprint and were met by a varied terrain with quite a number of hills and richly-forked courses. Here, Finland’s W16 team with Lotta Laakso, Anni Jantunen and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOF continues the course towards less climate emissions]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72127</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/iof-continues-the-course-towards-less-climate-emissions/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T12:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Orienteering Federation is still well on its way to achieving its goals for lowering climate emissions. This appears from IOF’s Carbon Budget Report for 2023, which estimates the CO2 emissions of the federation in the past year and has just been released. The report has been created by IOF’s Environment and Sustainability Commission […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ballarat Classics Series #3 – Nyaninyuk / Mt Beckworth – Sunday 30 June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13718</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/ballarat-classics-series-3-nyaninyuk-mt-beckworth-sunday-30-june/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T04:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eureka Orienteers invite you to Nyaninyuk / Mt Beckworth on Sunday, the 30th of June.
Ballarat Classics Series #3 – Nyaninyuk / Mt Beckworth – Sunday 30 June first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margi Freemantle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victorian Schools Team Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13716</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/victorian-schools-team-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T04:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to our Victorian Schools Team members, who have been selected to compete in the 2024 Australian Schools Championships in NSW this spring. 
Victorian Schools Team Announcement first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margi Freemantle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EYOC: Fast sprint in central Szczechin saw new nations rise to the top]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72119</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/eyoc-fast-sprint-in-central-szczechin-saw-new-nations-rise-to-the-top/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T18:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The more than 400 athletes at European Youth Orienteering Championships found the fast shoes from the bag on Sunday afternoon, when the EYOC Sprint race took place in central Szczechin. And compared to yesterday’s long distance forest race, there were three new faces on top of the four EYOC podiums after today’s race, which took […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Registration Extended | Pan-American Masters Games 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://neooc.com/?p=47397</id>
        <link href="https://neooc.com/registration-extended-pan-american-masters-games-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T01:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Registration deadline EXTENDED to June 26th Pan-American Masters Games 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Northeast Ohio Orienteering Club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EYOC: Long distance in tough, Polish hills]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72110</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/eyoc-long-distance-in-tough-polish-hills/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T16:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four different nations claimed the gold medals on the first day of European Youth Orienteering Championships, which take place in Szczechin, Poland this weekend. Saturday’s long distance tested the athletes’ physical abilities in the hilly terrain, where they also had to show their skills in coping with route planning on at least one long leg. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Szczechin ready to host EYOC this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=72089</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/szczechin-ready-to-host-eyoc-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T09:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 400 of the most talented young orienteers in Europe meet in Szczechin, Poland this weekend for the 2024 European Youth Orienteering Championships. The athletes compete in four classes W16, M16, W18 and M18 and three disciplines await: Long, Sprint and Relay. The forest terrain in northwestern Poland is rather hilly with eg. 280 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embargos announced for the 2026 World Masters MTBO Championships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54113</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/embargos-announced-for-the-2026-world-masters-mtbo-championships/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=embargos-announced-for-the-2026-world-masters-mtbo-championships"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2026 World Master Mountain Bike Orienteering Championships (MTBO) are being held in Moray between 3-7 June. The embargoes areas […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOA Accounts to 31st December 2023 available to view before AGM on Monday 24th June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54107</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/soa-accounts-to-31st-december-2023-available-to-view-before-agm-on-monday-24th-june/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=soa-accounts-to-31st-december-2023-available-to-view-before-agm-on-monday-24th-june"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SOA accounts for the year to 31st December 2023 have now been finalised and approved. They are available to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Tarr, Master Orienteer, Recognised in the News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13712</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/alex-tarr-master-orienteer-recognised-in-the-news/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T07:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOF welcomes new timing cooperation]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=71996</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/iof-welcomes-new-timing-cooperation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T09:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier in June, German company arntech GmbH – a sister company of IOF partner SPORTident GmbH – announced its acquisition of Norwegian timing company EMIT AS. The acquisition is expected to open new markets for SPORTident and EMIT products and give benefits for future development of timing products from SPORTident GmbH and EMIT AS. “Having […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Orienteer of the Year Award presented]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54100</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/young-orienteer-of-the-year-award-presented/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=young-orienteer-of-the-year-award-presented"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T07:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After long deliberations it was decided that the Young Orienteer of the Year award sponsored by Tulloch Homes for 2023 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamie Stevenson Trophy inspires enthusiasm despite the rain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54080</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/jamie-stevenson-trophy-inspires-enthusiasm-despite-the-rain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=jamie-stevenson-trophy-inspires-enthusiasm-despite-the-rain"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T06:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well there hasn’t been a damp Jamie Stevenson Trophy for a few years but a bit of rain did not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NZSSOC24 entries open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59799</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/nzssoc24-entries-open/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T23:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to give the heads up to your sports coordinators and get your entries in for the orienteering champs in the Wellington region for three days from the 19th-21st July 2024. Come and test your skills in new terrain and join in NZs biggest event for young orienteers. Direct entry link here For more info […]
NZSSOC24 entries open first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joolz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Important Closing Dates Coming Up Very Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5766</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/important-closing-dates-coming-up-very-soon/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reminder of important closing dates coming up very soon. The NI Urban League event at Craigavon South on Sunday 16 June, closes on Saturday 15 June at 14:00. All the details are on the event page on the LVO website and entries are at...
The post Important Closing Dates Coming Up Very Soon appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54057</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/young-leaders-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=young-leaders-2"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the JST hosts the presentation of the Young Orienteer of the Year Award this Sunday, it’s time to remind […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suzannerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jukola 2024: All You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://news.worldofo.com/?p=20095</id>
        <link href="https://news.worldofo.com/2024/06/14/jukola-2024-all-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T03:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 edition of Jukola – the largest orienteering relay in the world  – is organized the coming weekend with more than 3000 teams on the start in total! Start of the Jukola relay is Saturday at 22:00 CET (23:00 local time). 9 hours earlier at 13:00 CET the women start their relay. Here you find all ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Kocbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow Venla and Jukola relays on IOF TV this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=71983</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/follow-venla-and-jukola-relays-on-iof-tv-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 17.000 orienteers will set course for western Finland and one of the biggest orienteering competitions in the world, that happens this weekend. Venla and Jukola relays are gathering more than 3.000 teams in total in Lakia, where they will fight for the win in the tradition-rich relays from Saturday afternoon and until early […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Schools Festival 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54044</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/scottish-schools-festival-2024/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=scottish-schools-festival-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday was the Scottish School Orienteering Festival. This year the festival was organised by St Andrews Orienteering Club, Glasgow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>heidi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vic Series Double Header in Beechworth, June 22 and 23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13693</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/vic-series-double-header-in-beechworth-june-22-and-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't miss the chance to spend a weekend orienteering in Victoria's beautiful northeast - two Vic Series events on spectacular granite terrain!
Vic Series Double Header in Beechworth, June 22 and 23 first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tooting Commons Results]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22116</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/racereports/tooting-commons-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks for coming along to this week’s Park Race, and thanks to the Rose and Crown for hosting us. The race was organised by Nathan [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Orienteer of the Year Shortlist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54034</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/young-orienteer-of-the-year-shortlist-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=young-orienteer-of-the-year-shortlist-2"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We were thrilled to receive such amazing testaments to 2 juniors who have shown huge dedication to the sport. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suzannerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MelBushO is Back!  Candlebark Park, Sunday 30 June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13388</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/melbusho-is-back-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy a great introduction to orienteering at Candlebark Park in Templestowe, on Sunday 30 June. Online entry is open now!
MelBushO is Back!  Candlebark Park, Sunday 30 June first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NZSSOC map change – Long distance event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=59786</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/nzssoc-map-change-long-distance-event/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T10:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Change in venue for NZ Secondary School Orienteering Championships – Long distance event. Orienteering Wellington has made the decision to relocate the Long Distance event for the NZ Secondary School Orienteering Championships. Originally planned to take place near Porirua, the event will now be held at the Hydrabad map in Waitarere Beach. Waitarere Beach is […]
NZSSOC map change – Long distance event first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joolz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urban Planning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5758</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/urban-planning/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T08:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Urban orienteering has relaunched in 2024  Following the first event in Enniskillen on 28 April, we have two events in June. Sunday afternoon 16 June at Craigavon. All the details are on the LVO website with entries at SI Entries. Friday evening 21 June at...
The post Urban Planning appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event Advisers’ Clinic in Canada from August 12-13]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=71977</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/71977-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T07:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IOF’s FootO Commission organise an Event Advisers’ Clinic in Ottawa, Canada from August 12-13, 2024. The Clinic is organised for the education and recruitment of new IOF licensed Foot Orienteering Event Advisers. National orienteering federations are asked to identify and enter suitable candidates. Deadline for entries is June 30th. Go to the full invitation here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Park Race – Walpole & Lammas Parks, 2nd July]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22103</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/events/park-race-walpole-lammas-parks-2nd-july/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T10:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come to Ealing on Tuesday 2nd July 2024. and join us for the seventh race of London 2024 Park Series. Run on a new map [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World University Orienteering Championships Team Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11319</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/world-university-orienteering-championships-team-announced/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Australia is pleased to announce the following athletes have been selected to compete at the World University Orienteering Championships in Bankso, Bulgaria from 1-5 August, 2024.
World University Orienteering Championships Team Announced first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bushrangers Results and Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11309</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/bushrangers-results-and-recap/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Bushrangers visited NZ for an exciting weekend filled with thrilling and challenging orienteering.
Bushrangers Results and Recap first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May sees ScotJOS training in the Sun (for a change!)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54011</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/may-sees-scotjos-training-in-the-sun-for-a-change/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=may-sees-scotjos-training-in-the-sun-for-a-change"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ScotJOS enjoyed a weekend of fantastic sunshine for their latest camp in Perthshire. This was also the Last Blast, a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 AGM Booklet published]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54002</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/2024-agm-booklet-published/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2024-agm-booklet-published"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T16:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SOA AGM will take place on 24th June online at 7pm. Today we have published the AGM booklet in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capercaillie breeding season awareness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=53991</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/capercaillie-breeding-season-awareness/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=capercaillie-breeding-season-awareness"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scottish Orienteering Association has previously entered into an agreement with the Capercaillie Project that areas which are sensitive for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WORLD CUP ROUND 2 NEWS RECAP]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=11289</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/world-cup-round-2-news-recap/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup Round 2 had an individual sprint and relay sprint. See how our athletes performed in Genova, Italy.
WORLD CUP ROUND 2 NEWS RECAP first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Initial selections made for the Scotland team at the 2024 Senior Home Internationals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=53989</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/initial-selections-made-for-the-scotland-team-at-the-2024-senior-home-internationals/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=initial-selections-made-for-the-scotland-team-at-the-2024-senior-home-internationals"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As per the selection policy, the SOA has made some early selections for the team to represent Scotland at the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Park Street Update: Events June 19-25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13391</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/parkstreet-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GFR 2024 | Great Forest Rogaine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=59766</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/gfr-2024-great-forest-rogaine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T01:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Forest Rogaine is back for 2024 – starting from a new mystery location but still promising an awesome day out in Whakarewarewa Forest! 3 and 6 hour rogaine events with Foot and MTB options.  Get together a group of friends or family for a great adventure – you are guaranteed to go places […]
GFR 2024 | Great Forest Rogaine first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>