<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://design-o.github.io/orss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-10-16T06:12:23.134Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://design-o.github.io/orss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://design-o.github.io/orss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club Forum postponed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60576</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/club-forum-postponed/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Clubs and members, Due to low numbers, the Club Forum scheduled for Tue 22 October has been postponed. Regards Christo Peters General Manager
Club Forum postponed first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WMOC 2025 makes great efforts to meet summer heat issues]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74716</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/wmoc-2025-makes-great-efforts-to-meet-summer-heat-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T09:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next year’s World Masters Orienteering Championships in Girona, Spain are making great efforts to meet the challenges of the expected heat during the championship races. With race dates between August 9 – 15, it is likely that the masters athletes will be met by high temperatures. The organizers are very aware of this and therefore […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOF establishes prize on sustainability and orienteering]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74713</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/iof-establishes-prize-on-sustainability-and-orienteering/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T09:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IOF has established a prize and will from now on award the ‘Best scientific publication relating to Sustainability and Orienteering’ every two years. The prize shall reward the best research paper that considers the relationship between Orienteering and any or all of the core elements of Sustainability according to the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Shorts and Sprints Race 3, Tarralla Wetlands, Sunday 27 October – Entries Open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=14008</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/summer-shorts-and-sprints-race-3-tarralla-wetlands-sunday-27-october-entries-open/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T00:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hop to it - entries are open now for SSAS Race 3 on a fantastic, new colour map; parkland orienteering doesnt come much better than this!
Summer Shorts and Sprints Race 3, Tarralla Wetlands, Sunday 27 October – Entries Open first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nominations open: 2024 ASC SPORT VOLUNTEER OF THE YEAR AWARD]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12234</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/nominations-open-2024-asc-sport-volunteer-of-the-year-award/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T23:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The orienteering community can nominate a valued volunteer for the 2024 Australian Sports Commission Sport Volunteer of the Year Award.
Nominations open: 2024 ASC SPORT VOLUNTEER OF THE YEAR AWARD first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danielstott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invitation: IOF Event Adviser Seminar from November 23-24]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74634</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/iof-event-adviser-seminar-november-23-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IOF’s FootO Commission is organizing the IOF Event Adviser Seminar, which will be held online on November 23-24, 2o24. The seminar’s target group includes Senior Event Advisers and Event Advisers, but event organisers, athletes, federation officials, etc. are more than welcome to join. The program is divided into four blocks over the two weekend […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New series of webinars kick off on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74630</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/new-series-of-webinars-kick-off-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Wednesday, October 16th, the 2024-25 series of webinars organised by IOF’s Global Development Commission kick off. The first webinar bears the title “Prevention of injuries among young competitive orienteers” and features Martin Krause from Back In Business Physiotherapy. It is, among other things, about how to avoid injuries among young athletes and at the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a Hat Trick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=6061</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/its-a-hat-trick/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T09:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Possibly for the first time in orienteering history, the Home International Season has concluded with a win of Ireland over Wales at Senior, Veteran and now Junior level. Competing in East Anglia on 12-13 October, team Ireland juniors beat Wales 71 v 33 points, winning ...
The post It’s a Hat Trick appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Schools Orienteering Honour Team]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12222</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/australian-schools-orienteering-honour-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the following athletes named to the Australian Schools Orienteering Honour Team.
Australian Schools Orienteering Honour Team first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Junior Home International]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=6051</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/junior-home-international/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the final weekend of the Home International season, with the Juniors off to East Anglia on 12-13 October, with both the individual and relay events at Sheringham Park in Norfolk. Representing Team Ireland are: W14: Eimear Casey, Deirbhile Hassett, Aoife Masterson, Kathleen O’Donnell M14:...
The post Junior Home International appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Gortin to Glenarriff]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=6045</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/from-gortin-to-glenarriff/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After all the exitement of the NI Orienteering Championships at Gortin, the next Colour Series event at Glengarriff Forest, Co Antrim is creeping up fast! Colour Series 6 is hosted by LVO on Saturday 19 October, with entries to close on Monday 14 October at...
The post From Gortin to Glenarriff appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wimbledon Common Night-O, Tuesday 29th October]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22442</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/events/wimbledon-night-oct24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first race of South London Orienteers’ 2024-2025 Night series takes place on Wimbledon Common and Putney Heath, south-west London, on Tuesday 29th October 2024. Race Centre [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Clelland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Orienteering Championships 2024 Results & Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12185</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/australian-orienteering-championships-2024-results-recap/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Australian Orienteering Championships, held in Armidale, NSW from 28 September-6 October 2024, contained a plethora of events and activities for people of all ages.
Australian Orienteering Championships 2024 Results & Recap first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finland to host European Ski Orienteering Championships in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74611</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/finland-to-host-european-ski-orienteering-championships-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finland will host next year’s European Ski Orienteering Championships in the city of Posio from March 19 – 23, 2025 The races in the northeastern part of the country will at the same time serve as Junior World SkiO Championships and the European Youth SkiO Championships of 2025. The ESOC program features a Sprint relay, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South American Championships begin in Colombia on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74590</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/south-american-championships-begin-in-colombia-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T06:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colombia will welcome orienteers from six South American countries this weekend for the biannual South American Orienteering Championships. Athletes from Ecuador, Paraguay, Brazil, Uruguay, Chile and home nation Colombia have all signed up for the three races that make up SAOC 2024 in senior, junior and youth categories. The city of Marinilla will host the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLOW Night Series 2024-25]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22438</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/events/slow-night-series-2024-25/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SLOW night series will run from October until February and be comprised of 4 events. Full details on each event are posted here on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Clelland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peckham Street-O Results]]></title>
        <id>https://slow.org.uk/?p=22417</id>
        <link href="https://slow.org.uk/streeto/peckham-street-o-24-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T22:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a great start to the new Street-O series with over 90 people attending. Many thanks to James and Danny for organising the event [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vinh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Win the Stonewall Trophy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=6035</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/ireland-win-the-stonewall-trophy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T11:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time in seven years, Ireland have won back the Stonewall Trophy, on home turf in Co Tyrone. The Stonewall Trophy is hotly contested each year between Ireland and Wales at the Veteran Home International. Following the individual event at Gortin Glen Forest...
The post Ireland Win the Stonewall Trophy appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setters & Controllers Resource Sharing Meeting | New Date Wed 30 October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60530</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/setters-controllers-resource-sharing-meeting-new-date-wed-30-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T09:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ONZ is regularly asked for Setters and Controllers Resources, something we do not have. At the same time, we are aware that a number of clubs currently have some great resources to aid setting and controlling. The purpose of this meeting is threefold: We would love for all clubs to be represented at this meeting.  Please […]
Setters & Controllers Resource Sharing Meeting | New Date Wed 30 October first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Results | 2024 Medina Cross Country | Allardale County Park | Sunday, October 6th]]></title>
        <id>https://neooc.com/?p=47885</id>
        <link href="https://neooc.com/results-2024-medina-cross-country-allardale-county-park-sunday-october-6th/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T02:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Results Results listed by Team Captain Livelox – See route choices – Per course selection pull down]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Northeast Ohio Orienteering Club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the International TrailO course in Cyprus from Nov. 2-4]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74577</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/join-the-international-trailo-course-in-cyprus-from-nov-2-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T18:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Inclusive Orienteering for All” (IOFA) project is organising an International TrailO Training Course taking place from November 2 to 4, 2024 in Nicosia, Cyprus. This 2.5-day event is designed to equip participants with the knowledge and skills to organize and promote Trail Orienteering events that are inclusive and accessible to everyone, including individuals with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time to sign up for YLA Asia and Asian Coaching Clinic in December]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74581</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/time-to-sign-up-for-yla-asia-and-asian-coaching-clinic-in-december/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for an exciting opportunity with the IOF at Asian Orienteering Championships 2024. From 21st to 26th December 2024, a High-Level Development Programme for passionate coaches and orienteers – The Young Leader Academy Asia (YLA Asia) and the IOF Asian Coaching Clinic 2024 (AsCC) takes place in Chiang Mai, Thailand. Join fellow orienteering enthusiasts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controllers wanted for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54556</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/controllers-wanted-for-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=controllers-wanted-for-2025"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the 2025 calendar having been pulled together slightly later than anticipated due to the World Orienteering Championships having taken […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior Home Internationals see a home win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54538</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/senior-home-internationals-see-a-home-win/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senior-home-internationals-see-a-home-win"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 7th/ 8th September saw an opportunity for the Scottish athletes to compete on home turf, for the Senior Home […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 2024 NI Champions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=6005</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/congratulations-to-the-2024-ni-champions/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T16:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NI Long Distance Championships was run in surprisingly dry conditions, with the weather forecast suggesting heavy rain, at Gortin Glen Forest Park on Saturday 5 October. The event followed the Veteran Home Internationals with the top veterans from England, Ireland, Scotland and Wales competing....
The post Congratulations to the 2024 NI Champions appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Robertson recognised with the President’s Medal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54515</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/david-robertson-recognised-with-the-presidents-medal/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=david-robertson-recognised-with-the-presidents-medal"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T15:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Robertson of Edinburgh Southern Orienteering Club (ESOC) is never one to blow his own trumpet! So much so that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Junior Inter Regional Trophies find their way back to Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54489</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/junior-inter-regional-trophies-find-their-way-back-to-scotland/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=junior-inter-regional-trophies-find-their-way-back-to-scotland"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T13:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend saw a Scottish Junior team make their way to the South West for the Junior Inter Regional Championships. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Mapping Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.ie/?p=19485</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.ie/orienteering-mapping-course-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=orienteering-mapping-course-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T11:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Ireland is running its 4-weekly online course on Introduction to Mapping using OCAD software. The course is primarily aimed at those new to mapping, but all are welcome. Over a progressive series of four weekly online workshops participants will learn to: 1. Complete an urban sprint orienteering map that complies to international standards. 2. […]
The post Orienteering Mapping Course first appeared on Orienteering in Ireland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deirdre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 World Cup final round provides experience for next year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54491</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/world-cup-final-round-provides-experience-for-next-year/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=world-cup-final-round-provides-experience-for-next-year"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T09:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Peter Molloy (Forth Valley Orienteers) An impressive total of 10 Scottish or Scotland-based athletes have just returned from competing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans Running at Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5990</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/veterans-running-at-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best wishes to the Ireland Veteran Home International team, competing this weekend 4-5 October in Co Tryone. Of course the NI Orienteering Championships will be running the same courses after the veterans at Gortin Glen Forest on Saturday and then on Sunday the Veterans move...
The post Veterans Running at Home appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ballarat and Bendigo Events in October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13998</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/ballarat-and-bendigo-events-in-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T04:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Park Street Update: Summer Series is Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13391</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/parkstreet-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Series gets underway on September 30, and continues right through until March 2025.  Get ready!
Park Street Update: Summer Series is Here! first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portrush Results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5987</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/portrush-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:22:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trip to the seaside is usually relaxing, but after an energetic rush around the Portrush peninsula, a rest was required before getting the results pulled together. But now the results are posted at Fixtures & Results>2024 Results including RouteGadget along with the updated standings...
The post Portrush Results appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clubs sharing best practice over tea and cake]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54486</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/clubs-sharing-best-practice-over-tea-and-cake/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=clubs-sharing-best-practice-over-tea-and-cake"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Club Networking Day held on 14th September together with an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) to elect a new Chair […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikkihoward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the Finnish relay league final on IOF TV Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74546</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/follow-the-finnish-relay-league-final-on-iof-tv/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T12:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday, the 2024 Finnish relay league will be decided at Salo in southern Finland and it can be followed live on IOF TV. The final is the sixth stage of the league this year and for both women and men the overall victory is at stake. The final relays are three-legged for both men […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View from the Chair | September 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60519</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/orienteering-nz/view-from-the-chair-september-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T07:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been great getting back into ONZ stuff after a couple of months off with a newborn. It never ceases to amaze me the incredible people we have in our community who commit time and their professional skills to support our sport to improve and thrive. Our schools team are now in Australia for the Southern […]
View from the Chair | September 2024 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accuracy is everything  |  4th World Cup in Finland 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60516</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/accuracy-is-everything-4th-world-cup-in-finland-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[300 athletes from 32 nations have come together for the last World Cup this year on similar terrain for WOC 2025. These forested areas presented real challenges with sparse features and dense undergrowth.  Long distance – Thursday 26 September 2024 After numerous sprint and urban events, the team were happy to transition to Nordic forest […]
Accuracy is everything  |  4th World Cup in Finland 2024 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SISS & Canterbury School champs  | Christchurch  1-6 July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60513</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/schools/siss-canterbury-school-champs-christchurch-1-6-july/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The South Island School Champs incorporating the Canterbury School Champs was held recently on a sunny weekend in Christchurch with teams travelling from the far south as Invercargill right up to Nelson in the North. The first day involved a fun sprint course which took competitors though a primary school, park surrounds and some forested and […]
SISS & Canterbury School champs  | Christchurch  1-6 July  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A surge of popularity for orienteering  | Zespri Aims Games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60508</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/a-surge-of-popularity-for-orienteering-zespri-aims-games/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  Zespri AIMS Games School Sporting Championships introduced orienteering as a new sport for year 7 & 8 students. So a growing number of young adventurers tried orienteering for the first time, testing their spatial awareness and practicing using landmarks and maps to get around. Locals were surprised at the numbers entered as it was double […]
A surge of popularity for orienteering  | Zespri Aims Games first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tūāraki-North & Auckland Champs |  Labour day weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60503</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/tuaraki-north-auckland-champs-labour-day-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Counties Manukau Orienteering Club (CMOC) is looking forward to hosting the Tūāraki-North and Auckland Regional Championships 2024 over Labour Weekend, with three challenging and enjoyable events for orienteers from around the North Island and further afield. Please read the latest Bulletin . More details and information here:  Entries close: at 11:59pm on Monday 14 October 2024. Enter […]
Tūāraki-North & Auckland Champs |  Labour day weekend    first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSL Knock-out Sprint  |  Tuesday 22 April 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60494</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/high-performance/nsl-knock-out-sprint-tuesday-22-april-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Map: Christchurch location (within 30min drive of Christchurch Airport)Planners: Nathan Borton / Jacob KnoefController: Joe Lynch Following on from NZ Orienteering Champs (NZOC), there will be a NSL (National Sprint League) knock-out sprint in Christchurch. This will be part of the leaderboard event in the 2024/25 season. This is an additional event that is not part of the NZOC […]
NSL Knock-out Sprint  |  Tuesday 22 April 2025 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SISS 2025 & Otago Champs  |  Friday 25 & Saturday 26 April 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60490</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/siss-2025-otago-champs-friday-25-saturday-26-april-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weekend after Nationals (ANZAC weekend) will be the 2025 South Island Secondary schools The event doubles-up as the Otago champs with courses suitable for all ages. This is a spectacular time to make a trip south and be in the autumn colours.  For more information contact Dunedin Orienteering 
SISS 2025 & Otago Champs  |  Friday 25 & Saturday 26 April 2025 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oceania 2025 | Enter & order your shirt by December]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60485</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/event-news/international/oceania-2025-enter-order-your-shirt-by-december/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to get your entry (and shirt order) in! Entries close at midnight NZ time on Friday 3 January 2025 but shirt orders close earlier on Friday 20 December 2024.Head to: www.oceaniao.nz
Oceania 2025 | Enter & order your shirt by December first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Katoa Po Night relay & Explorer  |  8/9 March 2025 planning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60482</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/katoa-po-night-relay-explorer-8-9-march-2025-planning/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Planning for next year’s premier Night relay and the Katoa Po and Explorer weekend is well under way. The event will be held on two farms near Reporoa – one of which has not been used before and which contains a small but wonderful section of native bush which contains 3 very old, large native […]
Katoa Po Night relay & Explorer  |  8/9 March 2025 planning  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oceania 2026 Embargoes | Newcastle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60479</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/event-news/embargo/oceania-2026-embargoes-newcastle/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following areas are embargoed for use use for:  orienteering maps, training and route testing for by orienteers who wish to contest the Oceania Sprint Championship January 24-26th 2026.  These areas may not be entered for orienteering purposes: Information:Orienteering NSW – Embargoes (onsw.asn.au) Queries: President Central Coast Orienteers , Hilary Wood, Organiser (0408 843 627)
Oceania 2026 Embargoes | Newcastle first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2027 World Rogaining Champs  |  Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60476</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/2027-world-rogaining-champs-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T06:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian Rogaining Association is hosting the 2027 World Rogaining Championships for the region north of the city of Adelaide in the State of South Australia from 16-17 September. Paul Guard, President of the Australian Rogaining Association, said, “The iconic Flinders Ranges offer a visually stunning backdrop for the event and the area provides a variety of […]
2027 World Rogaining Champs  |  Australia first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entries open for 2024 Junior Camp|  13-18 December 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60473</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/entries-open-for-2024-junior-camp-13-18-december-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entries are now open for the Junior Camp! This year’s camp takes place in the New Plymouth. Entries will be open for the month of October.  All registrations are time-stamped so late entries will go onto a waiting list. To be eligible, students must be in years 9-13 and be regularly running red-level (or high […]
Entries open for 2024 Junior Camp|  13-18 December 2024  first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Youth Summer orienteering camp | School years 5-8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60470</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/2024-youth-summer-orienteering-camp-school-years-5-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What? This is a parent-led 3 day residential orienteering training camp at the start of the summer holiday.Who? All keen young orienteers, of any level / experience, up to and including yr 8 (yr 4 and below should be accompanied by a parent).When? Starting approx 5pm Friday 20 December, ending around 3pm, Sunday 22  December […]
2024 Youth Summer orienteering camp | School years 5-8 first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the coaches & team | The school leaders in Australia for the Southern Cross Challenge.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60461</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/schools/meet-the-coaches-team-the-school-leaders-in-australia-for-the-southern-cross-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Briana StevenBrian was in the schools team for three years, 2015-2017, so she has run in a few states. She has also achieved a good number of podiums over the years . Although she feels that best position she won she wasn’t actually on the podium, because she was beaten by three other NZ junior girls, […]
Meet the coaches & team | The school leaders in Australia for the Southern Cross Challenge. first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a short video | Be in to win Athena Luxe Protein bars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60457</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/create-a-short-video-be-in-to-win-athena-luxe-protein-bars/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This will be the first of a series of competitions and be-in-to-win Musashi or Athena protein bars. These bars have a creamy Luxe layer, coated in delicious no added sugar milk chocolate. It’s the perfect convenient protein snack on the go. Head here to get the low down on Athena Luxe Protein bars The CompetitionThe brief is simple […]
Create a short video | Be in to win Athena Luxe Protein bars first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NZMTBO champs- change of date  | 1&2 February, Otago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60454</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/nzmtbo-champs-change-of-date-12-february-otago/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fantastic weekend of competition, challenge, and fun for mountain bikers, orienteers, and adventure racers of all abilities. Add in the rogaine on the Monday for more nav riding.  The 2025 NZ MTBO Championships will be hosted by Dunedin Orienteering and held in Central Otago over the weekend of 1st / 2nd February, with a […]
NZMTBO champs- change of date  | 1&2 February, Otago first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOF Asian Coaching Clinic 2024  | Thailand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60451</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/iof-asian-coaching-clinic-2024-thailand/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2024 Asian Orienteering Championships (AsOC) from 21st to 26th December 2024 and you can also be a part of the launch of a new High-Level Development Programme for passionate coaches and orienteers alongside the The Young Leader Academy Asia (YLA Asia) and the IOF Asian Coaching Clinic (AsCC). Participants in the programme will […]
IOF Asian Coaching Clinic 2024  | Thailand first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coaching role in sunny climes  |  Queensland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60448</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/coaching-role-in-sunny-climes-queensland/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you like to spend 6 months in a sunny Queensland, visiting Australia’s best surf beaches and tropical rainforests… and coaching orienteering athletes? Applications from kiwi and international elite / experienced orienteers accepted.  In this role, you will: Questions? Send an  Email  Or apply today to become a Coach-in-Residence in Queensland
Coaching role in sunny climes  |  Queensland first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President & Club Leaders Forum | Tue 8 October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60445</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/president-club-leaders-forum-tue-8-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are holding our annual Presidents and Club leaders forum online, on Tue 8th Oct between 7:30 and 9:30pm. This is a chance for club leaders to get involved in discussions, share and learn about how different clubs are going as well as the sport overall. This year we are asking for club feedback to directly […]
President & Club Leaders Forum | Tue 8 October first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setters & Controllers Resource Sharing Meeting | Tue 15 October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60442</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/setters-controllers-resource-sharing-meeting-tue-15-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ONZ is regularly asked for Setters and Controllers Resources, something we do not have. At the same time, we are aware that a number of clubs currently have some great resources to aid setting and controlling. The purpose of this meeting is threefold: We would love for all clubs to be represented at this meeting.  Please […]
Setters & Controllers Resource Sharing Meeting | Tue 15 October first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club Forum | Tue 22 October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60439</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/club-forum-tue-22-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us to talk orienteering at the forum. You’ll have the chance to engage in meaningful discussions and share your insights. Don’t miss this opportunity to connect with others and contribute to the conversation. It will be in the evening on Tuesday 22nd October. Topics will be advised following the President’s Forum on Tue 22 September. Your presence […]
Club Forum | Tue 22 October first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrity in sport & recreation  |  Integrity Code Consultation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?p=60436</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/uncategorized/integrity-in-sport-recreation-integrity-code-consultation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T04:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please see attached a copy of the draft Integrity Code and the discussion document to mark the beginning of our public Below is the links to the draft Integrity Code and the discussion document to mark the beginning of our public consultation, which closes at 5pm on 1 November 2024.  The Integrity Code is a key […]
Integrity in sport & recreation  |  Integrity Code Consultation first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christo Peters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jump In To Orienteering!  Spooky Day at Tarantula Park – Free Fun for Families, Sunday 13 October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13956</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/jump-in-to-orienteering-spooky-day-at-tarantula-park-free-fun-for-families-sunday-13-october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T04:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NI Junior Team back from JIRCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5978</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/ni-junior-team-back-from-jircs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steph Pruzina, NIOA Junior Team Manager reports on the Junior Inter-Regional Championships… This year, a small NIOA squad set off for the Junior Inter-Regional Championships hosted in the Bristol area by NGOC and BOK. Between them Euan Kennedy and Emma Graham hatched a plan to...
The post NI Junior Team back from JIRCs appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event officials courses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54473</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/event-officials-courses/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=event-officials-courses"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T12:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clubs are always looking for more volunteers to take on event official roles and help spread the load. Would you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suzannerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup Final 2024: Maps, Results and Splits Analysis]]></title>
        <id>http://news.worldofo.com/?p=20363</id>
        <link href="https://news.worldofo.com/2024/09/30/world-cup-final-2024-maps-results-race-development-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T07:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tove Alexandersson (Sweden) won both the long distance, the middle distance and anchored Sweden to victory on the women’s relay in this weekend’s World Cup final in Kuopio, Finland. In the men’s class Miika Kirmula (Finland) won the long distance, Eirik Langedal Breivik (Norway) the middle distance and Sweden won the relay. In the Long ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Kocbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweden takes the Team World Cup title after thrilling relay wins]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74509</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/sweden-takes-the-team-world-cup-title-after-thrilling-relay-wins/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T16:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing was decided in the overall Orienteering Team World Cup before Sunday’s relays north of Kuopio in Finland, where this year’s World Cup Final took place. Before the start of the men’s relay, Switzerland led the overall standings – 13 points ahead of Norway and a 51-point lead over the defending champions from Sweden. And […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Bushrangers Team Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12163</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/australian-bushrangers-team-announced/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T02:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Bushrangers team athletes have been chosen for the AUS vs. NZ Test Match Championships.
Australian Bushrangers Team Announced first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup victories for Aebersold and Fosser – but neither won their Middle race]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74426</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/world-cup-victories-for-aebersold-and-fosser-but-neither-won-their-middle-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T13:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss athlete Simona Aebersold and Kasper Harlem Fosser, Norway were both second today, the race winners being Tove Alexandersson, Sweden and the European Middle Distance champion, Norwegian Eirik Langedal Breivik. Both in technique and speed, these two were outstanding today. Aebersold’s victory ends a run of 9 World Cup wins overall in succession for Alexandersson, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clive</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Shorts and Sprints Coming Soon!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13930</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/summer-shorts-and-sprints-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T01:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Shorts and Sprints are coming soon!  Get excited for 9 amazing races
Summer Shorts and Sprints Coming Soon! first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Orienteering Championships 2024 Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12156</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/australian-orienteering-championships-2024-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T17:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year's Australian Orienteering Championships will take place from 28 September - 6 October in and around Armidale and Uralla.
Australian Orienteering Championships 2024 Preview first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Your NIOC Entry In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5972</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/get-your-nioc-entry-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t miss out on the best event of the year – The 2025 Northern Ireland Long Distance Chamionships, taking place at Gortin Glen Forest on Sat 5 October. Entries close at 23:00 Saturday 28 September so be sure to make your entry on SI Entries...
The post Get Your NIOC Entry In appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup Final, Long race: Tove Alexandersson on top form]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74171</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/world-cup-final-long-race-tove-alexandersson-on-top-form/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tove Alexandersson, Sweden and Miika Kirmula, Finland were the stars of the Long Distance race today, held at the same venue as next year’s World Orienteering Championships – Kuopio, Finland. The women’s race winner provided yet another master-class, with a lead at the finish 4.05 over current World Cup leader Simona Aebersold SUI. Hanna Lundberg […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clive</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 NZ Pinestar team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60424</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/2024-nz-pinestar-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T09:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to those selected for the Pinestars team.  The NZ team for the 4 AUS / NZ Test Match races at Australian Champs include this weekend’s Relay and Middle distance events, and then the following weekend with the Long distance and the Sprint distance.
2024 NZ Pinestar team first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joolz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful Introduction to Orienteering for the Deaf Community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54457</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/successful-introduction-to-orienteering-for-the-deaf-community/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=successful-introduction-to-orienteering-for-the-deaf-community"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T16:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Saturday, SOA organised an Introduction to Orienteering course with the British Deaf Association Scotland. Held in Alexandra Park in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>louise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NI Team off to the JIRCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5945</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/ni-team-off-to-the-jircs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Northern Ireland junior sqaud are off to the Junior Inter Regional Championships “JIRCs” this weekend 27-29 September, hosted by SWOA. The events will be held on on Mallard Pike and Mendip near Bristol. Travelling are: M18 Peter Gamble, W18 Anastasia Maglich and Emma Graham....
The post NI Team off to the JIRCs appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vale Bob Allison]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12149</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/vale-bob-allison/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T10:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian orienteering has lost one of its most accomplished and popular participants with the passing of Bob Allison on 21 September, following a long illness.
Vale Bob Allison first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaeldowling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup Final 2024: All You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://news.worldofo.com/?p=20351</id>
        <link href="https://news.worldofo.com/2024/09/25/world-cup-final-2024-all-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T03:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with a long distance race on Thursday – and continuing with a middle distance on Saturday and a relay on Sunday – the World’s best orienteers will gather in Kuopio, Finland to compete for the final time on the international scene this season. The terrain looks amazing as always in this region of Finland, and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Kocbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to follow the World Cup Final in Finland]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74098</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/how-to-follow-the-world-cup-final-in-finland/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T08:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 international orienteering season will go off with a bang, when the World Cup Final is held in Finland from Thursday to Sunday this week. Whether you follow from the arena north of Kuopio or from home, you should be in good hands getting close to the action in the forest. IOF TV offers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering World Cup Final – 26-29 September – Kuopio, Finland]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12121</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/orienteering-world-cup-final-26-29-september-kuopio-finland/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T00:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Orienteering World Cup Final / Round 4 in Kuopio, Finland begins on Thursday. Follow all the live services on the IOF homepage.
Orienteering World Cup Final – 26-29 September – Kuopio, Finland first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>arpadk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Andrine Benjaminsen on the World Cup Final and Norway’s medal rush at EOC]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74091</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/podcast-andrine-benjaminsen-on-the-world-cup-final-and-norways-medal-rush-at-eoc/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T19:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrine Benjaminsen (NOR) played a big role in Norway’s impressive performances at EOC in Hungary, where the Norwegians took seven medals and topped the medal standings. She won a relay silver and two individual bronze medals in the Hungarian heat and has hit a good shape this fall and look forward to the World Cup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Members Please Join the NIOA EGM on Zoom – Tues 24 Sep at 19:30]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5937</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/members-please-join-the-nioa-egm-on-zoom-tues-24-sep-at-1930/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members are kindly requested to join on Zoom on Tuesday 24 September at 19:30 for a short Extra Ordinary General Meeting. As the meeting is to consider a change to the Constitution at least 25 members are required to be present at the meeting. Therefore...
The post Members Please Join the NIOA EGM on Zoom – Tues 24 Sep at 19:30 appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland’s Elite Poised to Dominate the Thrilling World Cup!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.ie/?p=19467</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.ie/irelands-elite-poised-to-dominate-the-thrilling-world-cup/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=irelands-elite-poised-to-dominate-the-thrilling-world-cup"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Ireland is excited to announce that six talented athletes will represent Ireland at the World Cup Final in Finland. The team includes Aoife, Clodagh, Colm, Cílín, Ruairi, and Laurence. They will compete internationally starting on September 26th. The final races for the 2024 Orienteering World Cup will take place in Kuopio, Finland, from Thursday […]
The post Ireland’s Elite Poised to Dominate the Thrilling World Cup! first appeared on Orienteering in Ireland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Senior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big News From Bulgaria – Maya Places 4th in Her First World MTBO Champs!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13882</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/big-news-from-bulgaria-maya-places-4th-in-her-first-world-mtbo-champs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T10:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic results coming in from Maya and Lucas at the World MTBO Champs!
Big News From Bulgaria – Maya Places 4th in Her First World MTBO Champs! first appeared on Orienteering Victoria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the West Woods for a Greater Good | Jonathan Boyer]]></title>
        <id>https://neooc.com/?p=47860</id>
        <link href="https://neooc.com/exploring-the-west-woods-for-a-greater-good-jonathan-boyer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T20:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEOOC’s Jonathan Boyer wrote a fantastic article for the Geauga Park District’s News Magazine: the Park Explorer See the full article here: Exploring the West Woods for a Greater Good Find more information about the Geauga County Park District here: www.geaugaparkdistrict.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Northeast Ohio Orienteering Club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Event | The aMAIZEing Night-O! | Near Peninsula, Ohio | Saturday, October 26th]]></title>
        <id>https://neooc.com/?p=47855</id>
        <link href="https://neooc.com/new-event-the-amaizeing-night-o-near-peninsula-ohio-saturday-october-26th/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aMAIZEing Night-O! | Near Peninsula, Ohio | Saturday, October 26th]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Northeast Ohio Orienteering Club</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final battle for 2024 World Cup titles in Finland]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.sport/?p=74012</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.sport/final-battle-for-2024-world-cup-titles-in-finland/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T08:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final battle for the 2024 Orienteering World Cup titles takes place in Kuopio, Finland from Thursday to Sunday. The forest races count as the fourth round in this year’s Orienteering World Cup, which has previously taken us to fast and demanding sprint races in Switzerland and Italy and most recently a series of tough […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erling Thisted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54410</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/juniors/young-leaders-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=young-leaders-3"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juniors – are you a keen orienteer who would like to start getting involved in volunteering?  Club volunteer coordinators – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suzannerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Junior Interareas 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54401</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/junior-interareas-2024/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=junior-interareas-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T15:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Junior Interarea weekend will take place on the 26/27th October. This is a weekend of interarea competition between the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>heidi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nominations – Aus/NZ Challenge at Oceania 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12074</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/nominations-aus-nz-challenge-at-oceania-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T00:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OA is calling for nominations from eligible Australian orienteers who would like to take part in the next Aus/NZ Challenge, to be held in conjunction with the Oceania Championships in New Zealand from 24-27 January, 2025. The Challenge consists of a sprint, middle, long and relay. However, you are still eligible to nominate for the team if […]
Nominations – Aus/NZ Challenge at Oceania 2025 first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>arpadk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organiser workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54391</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/juniors/organiser-workshops/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=organiser-workshops"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T15:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever fancied helping out your club by organising an event or been asked to but it all seemed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suzannerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vics at the AusChamps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/?p=13937</id>
        <link href="https://www.vicorienteering.asn.au/vics-at-the-auschamps/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T06:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Debbie Dodd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Young People’s Sport Panel is now recruiting!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/?p=54371</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottish-orienteering.org/news/the-young-peoples-sport-panel-is-now-recruiting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-young-peoples-sport-panel-is-now-recruiting"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T15:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Young People’s Sport Panel has applications open for its seventh cohort of members. If you’re aged 14-23, living in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>louise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entries Open for the NI Champs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/?p=5932</id>
        <link href="https://www.niorienteering.org.uk/entries-open-for-the-ni-champs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T09:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entries are open on SI Entries for the NI Long Distance Championships in Gortin Glen Forest on Sat 5 October. All the details are on the Fermanagh Orienteers website. This classic orienteering area has been recently remapped and extended. The event takes place alongside the...
The post Entries Open for the NI Champs appeared first on NI Orienteering Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NIOA Secretary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANZ MTBO Challenge Team Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://orienteering.asn.au/?p=12055</id>
        <link href="https://orienteering.asn.au/anz-challenge-team-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orienteering Australia is pleased to announce the team to ride against New Zealand in the ANZ Challenge during the forthcoming Australian MTBO Champs to be held in the ACT on 18-20 October 2024.
ANZ MTBO Challenge Team Announced first appeared on Orienteering Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elizabethl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 Nationals embargo effective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.orienteering.org.nz/?post_type=news&amp;p=60399</id>
        <link href="https://www.orienteering.org.nz/news/2025-nationals-embargo-effective/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T06:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone intending to enter Nationals 2025 needs to be aware of the embargoes in place for the event. Embargoes are areas that are out of bounds to competitors prior to the events, and cover the areas used in the competition. This prevents unfair prior knowledge being gained about the terrain and map features, and helps […]
2025 Nationals embargo effective first appeared on Orienteering New Zealand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joolz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>